(Penny:)Seriously?
You went first after only two weeks?
(Penny:)That's bold.
(Leonard:)It's not bold, it's a mistake.
(Leonard:)I didn't change my status.
(Penny:)Well, then who did?
(Sheldon:)I had no choice. He cried in front of her.
(Leonard:)You hacked my Facebook account?
(Sheldon:)Oh, it's hardly hacking when you use
the same password for everything, Kal-El.
(Leonard:)Are you insane?
Now she's gonna think I'm desperate.
(Leonard:)You've destroyed this relationship.
And you wanna know
the worst part?
You don't understand
what you did wrong...
(Leonard:)...because you can't conceive of something
that you are not an expert in.
- In which I am not an expert.
- Don't even...
Don't wanna hear another word
out of you.
(Leonard:)Ooh.
(Penny(after Raj lets out a noise):)What's wrong, Lassie?
Timmy fall down the well?
(Penny(after Raj lets out a noise):)Oh, wow.
(Penny(after Raj lets out a noise):)She just updated her Facebook status.
"Stephanie Barnett is in a relationship
with Leonard Hofstadter."
(Penny:)Really?
(Leonard:)Oh, look at that.
I have a girlfriend. Ha, ha.
(Sheldon:)If I am permitted to speak again...
(Sheldon:)...Dr. Sheldon Cooper for the win.